<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leaders</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:27:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/leaders/</guid><description>Sebastian Poulose Trustee &amp;amp; Pastoral Council Member Binish Mathew Trustee &amp;amp; Pastoral Council Member Vishal Jose Mannanal Trustee &amp;amp; Pastoral Council Member Jimmy Paul Isaac Pastoral Council Member Jacob Thomas Pastoral Council Member Sheen Thomas Pastoral Council Member Betty Chempananical Pastoral Council Member &amp;amp; Director of Religious Education Sajay Jose Assistant Director of Religious Education Shikha Jose Women Fellowship Council Member Ginny Ajith Women Fellowship Council Member Nisha Susan John Women Fellowship Council Member</description></item><item><title>About CCD</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about-ccd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about-ccd/</guid><description>Motto Be Alive to God (Gal. 2/19) Vision We envisage to motivate our young ones to Learn, Love, Live and Proclaim Jesus, the Lord and God in and through the Church as Syro Malabar Catholics in the present U.S. context.
Mission To prepare persons to live authentic Catholic lives in a culture that is increasingly diverse, complex and challenging To teach to carry on the Treasury of Faith and Tradition of the Syro Malabar Church To form spiritually, morally, emotionally, socially, mature disciples of the Lord To help persons to live a counter-cultural life of witnessing Along with the above tasks, the CCD also aims at fulfilling the following tasks of catechesis:</description></item><item><title>CCD Associations</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-associations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-associations/</guid><description>Holy Childhood Association (HCA) Holy Childhood is an association of children who have not received First Holy Communion. It is an organization set up to mold the religious life of growing children and instills wisdom and Christian values in them so that they grow up as valuable for the family, the Church, the society and God. The main aim is to make the little children filled with love for Infant Jesus, to encourage them to do little services motivated by the love of Infant Jesus.</description></item><item><title>CCD Guidelines</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-guidelines/</guid><description>Registration Registration will be done online. Registration form for the upcoming year will be available in June. Parents must register their children by the end of June to facilitate the ordering of textbooks. Students will be assigned to classes based on their age. Registration fees will be $150 per child or $300 per family. Payments can me made through one of the following ways: : Check made out to Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission Seattle WA.</description></item><item><title>CCD Team</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-team/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-team/</guid><description>CCD Team MISSION DIRECTOR FR. JAMES JOSEPH PRINCIPAL BETTY CHEMPANANICAL VICE PRINCIPAL SAJAY JOSE VICE PRINCIPAL TOM MANNANCHERY GRADE KG-A ANNAMARY BABU SITHARA GEORGE GRADE KG-B DAINY KOTTOOR DHANYA FRANCIS GRADE 1 SONA SEBASTIAN SEEMA LUKOSE GRADE 2-A PRIYANKA NIRMALA JOSE GRADE 2-B ANU ANAND JOHN SHILPA XAVIER GRADE 2-C MINTA THOMAS ANU JOHN GRADE 3 JERIN MATHEW TUNI MUNDACKAL GRADE 4-A ANNA MATHEW AMRITA JACOB KARIPAT GRADE 4-B JAMES DOMINIC NIKHILA ROSE GRADE 5 NISHA JOHN RAJESH GEORGE GRADE 6-A AMITHA MATHEW JISS JOSE GRADE 6-B JACOB NINAN TINTU JOSE GRADE 7 JOSEPH JOHN MANU VARGHESE GRADE 8 JEESMON JACOB ANISH MONY GRADE 9 THOMAS P.</description></item><item><title>CCD Theme</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-theme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-theme/</guid><description>Give Glory to God Eesho Mishihaykku Sthuthi Aayirikkatte ഈശോ മിശിഹായ്ക്ക് സ്തുതി ആയിരിക്കട്ടെ So, whether you eat or drink, or whatever you do, do everything for the glory of God. (1 Cor 10:31)
Growing up, we were taught to say Eesho mishihaykku sthuthi aayirikkatte, to our parents, our elders, fathers and sisters - not just as a sign of respect but also to give praise to the Lord. It is that virtue that we intend to teach and practice with the children this year.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about/</guid><description>Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission, is made up of vibrant, faithful people who serve our Mission and community in numerous ways – from worship, religious education and formation, sacramental preparation and spiritual development, to community outreach and social activities. We strive to be a welcoming community that reflects the heart, mercy and teachings of Christ, under the obedience of the Roman Catholic Church through the tradition of the Syro Malabar Rite.</description></item><item><title>Announcements</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/announcements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/announcements/</guid><description>Oct 15th, 2023 Announcements from Sunday School We have sent a detailed email about the camp to all registered families. We invite the community to attend Sunday Qurbana at camp with the children at 2:30pm celebrated by Fr.Joseph Alex and our mission Director Fr. James Joseph. We request your prayers for the success of this spiritual retreat for our children.
A gentle reminder to families who are yet to pay $150 to cover CCD expenses.</description></item><item><title>CCD Calendar</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/calendar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/calendar/</guid><description> Monthly Events Calendar Annual Calendar</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/contact/</guid><description> Address 8512 122nd Ave NE, Suite 227, Kirkland, WA 98033
Email smcseattle.trustees@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/events/</guid><description>November 2023 All Saints Day Winners 2023 Group A 1st Prize Evelyn Miriam Charles(Our Lady of Fatima) 2nd Prize Annlyn Chalissery (St.Alphonsa) 3rd Prize Ebner Sheen(St.James) Group B 1st Prize Alka Sheen(St. Philomina) 2nd Prize Rachel Maria Thomas(St. Rita) 3rd Prize Annmaria Manu (St. Maria Goretti) 3rd Prize Kevin Tom Augustine (St.John the Baptist) Group C 1st Prize Andrea Chalissery (Our Lady of Fatima) 2nd Prize Leo Thomas (St. Maximilian Kolbe) 3rd Prize Sarah Liz George (St.</description></item><item><title>Online Donation</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/donation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/donation/</guid><description>All donations and payments to Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission can now be made through Tithe.ly which is built for churches and ministries to securely process your donations and payments.
Tithe.ly will issue a year-end giving statement for all your online donations.
Your donations are greatly appreciated and especially needed to support and maintain our ministries. Please prayerfully consider to make a recurring donation. Thank you.
Donate</description></item><item><title>Online Forms</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/online-forms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/online-forms/</guid><description>Holy Family Syro-Malabar Catholic Mission Registration
Mass Intentions
Oppis</description></item><item><title>Parish On Net</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/parish-on-net/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/parish-on-net/</guid><description>ParishOnNet website enables the head of a family to update the details of every one in the family. This data is confidential and would help Chicago diocese to plan better for Seattle SyroMalabar Community.
FAQs 1. What is ParishOnNet?
ParishOnNet is an online church management system mandated by St. Thomas SyroMalabar Diocese of Chicago for its parishes and missions. It offers standard parish management features along with facilities for online payment and a parishioner portal.</description></item></channel></rss>