<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:27:13 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leaders</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:27:13 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/leaders/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="trustees">Trustees&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Betty Chempananical&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Biju Mathew&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sonimon James&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="parish-council-members">Parish Council Members&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Anu Anand&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Arun Mathew&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Bibin Baby&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Binish Mathew&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Minta Thomas&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Saji Alex&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sheena Mathew&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Sunil John&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tintu Mathew&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="ministry-leads">Ministry Leads&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Communications Ministry - Cijo Thomas&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Food &amp;amp; Fellowship Ministry - Ajith Jose, Chrison Jacob&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Hospitality Ministry - Thomas Mathew, Nithin Jose&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Liturgical Ministry ( Altar Servers) - Manu Varghese&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Liturgical Ministry (Altar Guild) - Minta Thomas&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Music Ministry - Jerin Mathew &amp;amp; Liz George&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Religious Education Ministry - Sajay Jose&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Outreach Ministry - Nissy Joseph&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Tech Ministry - Tom Chempananical&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Women&amp;rsquo;s Fellowship Ministry - Asha Joseph, Amalu Johns&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>About CCD</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about-ccd/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about-ccd/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="motto">Motto&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="be-alive-to-god-gal-219">Be Alive to God (Gal. 2/19)&lt;/h4>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="vision">Vision&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>We envisage to motivate our young ones to Learn, Love, Live and Proclaim Jesus, the Lord and God in and through the Church as Syro Malabar Catholics in the present U.S. context.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="mission">Mission&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>To prepare persons to live authentic Catholic lives in a culture that is increasingly diverse, complex and challenging&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To teach to carry on the Treasury of Faith and Tradition of the Syro Malabar Church&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To form spiritually, morally, emotionally, socially, mature disciples of the Lord&lt;/li>
&lt;li>To help persons to live a counter-cultural life of witnessing&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Along with the above tasks, the CCD also aims at fulfilling the following tasks of catechesis:&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CCD Associations</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-associations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-associations/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="holy-childhood-association-hca">Holy Childhood Association (HCA)&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Holy Childhood is an association of children who have not received First Holy Communion. It is an organization set up to mold the religious life of growing children and instills wisdom and Christian values in them so that they grow up as valuable for the family, the Church, the society and God. The main aim is to make the little children filled with love for Infant Jesus, to encourage them to do little services motivated by the love of Infant Jesus.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CCD Guidelines</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-guidelines/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="registration">Registration&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Registration will be done online. Registration form for the upcoming year will be available in June.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents must register their children by the end of June to facilitate the ordering of textbooks.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Students will be assigned to classes based on their age.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Registration fees will be $150 per child or $300 per family. Payments can me made through one of the following ways: :
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Check&lt;/strong> made out to &lt;strong>Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission Seattle WA&lt;/strong>. Mention &lt;strong>Child&amp;rsquo;s name - CCD&lt;/strong> in the memo. Cheques can be given to Sebastian Poulose(Trustee, Holy Family Mission) at church during weekly Qurbana.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Cash&lt;/strong> payment to Sebastian Poulose(Trustee, Holy Family Mission) at church during weekly Qurbana.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Online&lt;/strong> &lt;a href="https://holyfamilyseattle.org/donation/">here&lt;/a>. Select &lt;strong>CCD ministry&lt;/strong> from the dropdown and in the memo section, mention &lt;strong>CCD Registration&lt;/strong>.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="ccd-classes">CCD Classes&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>CCD academic year will start in September and end in June.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>CCD program will follow the curriculum and guidelines established by the Department of Catechesis, St. Thomas Syro Malabar Catholic Diocese of Chicago.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>CCD classes will be conducted under the direction of the Mission Director and taught by parent volunteers.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>CCD classes will be run in a hybrid fashion.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Online classes will be conducted via Google Meet/Teams.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>In-person classes once a month will be conducted before the regular Syro-Malabar mass.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Extra classes will be added at the discretion of the Mission Director and CCD team&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="exams-and-grades">Exams and Grades&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>There will be two exams in an academic year: 1st Semester exam in January and 2nd Semester exam in June.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Grade Completion certificates l are issued on successfully completing the requirements of each grade&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The total grade for the academic year shall be based on the following categories:&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;br>
&lt;table style="width:30%">
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>CATEGORY&lt;/b> &lt;/td>&lt;td> &lt;b>WEIGHT&lt;/b> &lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>Attendance&lt;/td>&lt;td>10%&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>Homework&lt;/td>&lt;td>20%&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>Participation&lt;/td>&lt;td>10%&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>Exams&lt;/td>&lt;td>60%&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;/table>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Final grade is awarded as follows:&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;br>
&lt;table style="width:30%">
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>PERCENTAGE&lt;/b> &lt;/td>&lt;td> &lt;b>LETTER GRADE&lt;/b> &lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>90% - 100%&lt;/td>&lt;td>A&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>80% - 89%&lt;/td>&lt;td>B&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>70% - 79%&lt;/td>&lt;td>C&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>60% - 69%&lt;/td>&lt;td>D&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td>Below 60%&lt;/td>&lt;td>F&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;/table>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="safety">Safety&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>All teachers will undergo VIRTUS training as well as be familiarized with the Diocesan safe environment policies related to online learning.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Every class will have two adult teachers assigned to it.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>We do not collect the information that is not necessary to run the C.C.D program. No adult can ask a child (children) for any such information.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parent’s consent is necessary to allow their children to take online classes.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents should monitor their children’s online activity for any child who is below 18.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="student-conduct">Student Conduct&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Students are expected to attend all classes regularly. We will strictly adhere to the guidelines provided by the diocese.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents must inform teachers of their Child’s absence ahead of time.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Teachers will contact parents about uninformed absences and tardiness.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Students with full attendance are eligible to receive Full attendance awards during graduation.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Students are always expected to dress in their best attire for class. “Sunday best” is the recommended attire.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Respect to all CCD staff and students is expected from students at all times.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>During online classes, teachers will ask the children to keep their video on to engage them and encourage their full participation.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Children are requested to comply with the safe environment policy and appropriate behavior in class. If any issue arises, such as bullying, inappropriate behavior, or improper use of media with regards to church or CCD, it must be reported and addressed promptly.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Teachers will not allow a child to leave early, without a request from parents.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Students are encouraged to attend the Syro-Malabar Catholic Holy Mass on Sundays after CCD classes.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h3 id="parent-responsibilities">Parent Responsibilities&lt;/h3>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Parents will be responsible for monitoring their child&amp;rsquo;s behavior while attending classes virtually.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents of young children will be asked to sit with their children during class.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents are encouraged to be actively engaged in extending the learning beyond the classroom and help the children learn prayers and bible verses at home.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents are encouraged to join the parents’ Whatsapp group. Please connect with one of the DREs for details.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Parents are requested to consider taking one of the following volunteer roles, which help with smooth functioning of the CCD programs:
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>a teacher (assigned as a co-teacher of a class)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>a backup teacher (called to fill in as needed in any class)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>PTA member (help organize activities and events)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>CCD Team</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-team/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-team/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="ccd-team">CCD Team&lt;/h3>
&lt;table>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>MISSION DIRECTOR&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>FR. RAPHAEL AMBADAN&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>PRINCIPAL&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>SAJAY JOSE&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>VICE PRINCIPAL&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>TOM MANNANCHERY&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>VICE PRINCIPAL&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>SONIA JACOB&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE KG-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>SITHARA GEORGE&lt;/td> &lt;td>NITA BINISH&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE KG-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>ANNAMARY BABY&lt;/td> &lt;td>JANCY JOESEPH&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 1-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>GINNY GEORGE&lt;/td> &lt;td>SONA SEBASTIAN&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 1-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>MINTA THOMAS&lt;/td> &lt;td>ANU JOHN&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 2-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>ANU ANAND JOHN&lt;/td> &lt;td>SHILPA XAVIER&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 2-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>DAINY KOTTOOR&lt;/td> &lt;td>DHANYA FRANCIS&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 3-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JERIN MATHEW&lt;/td> &lt;td>ARUJA SIJO THOMMANA&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 3-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>NEETHU JOESEPH&lt;/td> &lt;td>RIYA TOMY KONDODY&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 4&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>STEPHIN JOESEPH ANNA&lt;/td> &lt;td>AMRITA JACOB KARIPAT&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 5-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>NISHA JOHN&lt;/td> &lt;td>VISHAL JOSE MANNANAL&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 5-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>RAJESH GEORGE&lt;/td> &lt;td>MEJO CHERIAN&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 6-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JISS JOSE&lt;/td> &lt;td>MARIA ROSE&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 6-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JACOB NINAN&lt;/td> &lt;td>JAMES DOMINIC&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 7-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JOSEPH JOHN&lt;/td> &lt;td>BINCY MATTHEW&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 7-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>MANU VARGHESE&lt;/td> &lt;td>ASHIN TINTO&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 8-A&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JEESMON JACOB&lt;/td> &lt;td>NIDHIN JOSE&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 8-B&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>ANISH MONY&lt;/td> &lt;td>MELVY ALBERT&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 9&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>THOMAS P. THOMAS&lt;/td> &lt;td>JERRY&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 10&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JIMMY ISSAC&lt;/td> &lt;td>TOM CHEMPANANICAL&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 11&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>SUNIL JOHN&lt;/td> &lt;td>MOLLY GEORGE&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>GRADE 12&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>TOJI MATTHEW&lt;/td> &lt;td>DANNY VAYALIL&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;/table>
&lt;table>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>HOLY CHILDHOOD ASSOCIATION (HCA)&lt;/b>&lt;/td>&lt;td>AMITHA MATHEW&lt;br>JULIN JOSE&lt;br>DHANYA FRANCIS&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>CHERUPUSHPA
MISSION LEAGUE
(CML)&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>NIKHILA ROSE &lt;br> SHERINE THOMAS &lt;br> SONA SEBASTIAN &lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>DIOCESAN YOUTH APOSTOLATE (DYA)&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>JOBIN JOESEPH&lt;br>TINTU JOSE&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>&lt;td> &lt;b>SACRAMENTAL PREPARATION&lt;/b> &lt;/td> &lt;td>LIZ GEORGE PHILIP &lt;br>NISSY JOSEPH&lt;br>AMITHA MATHEW&lt;br>BINISH MATHEW&lt;br>JIMMY ISSAC&lt;/td>&lt;td>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>
&lt;/table></description></item><item><title>CCD Theme</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-theme-2023-2024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-theme-2023-2024/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="give-glory-to-god">&lt;strong>Give Glory to God&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;h4 id="eesho-mishihaykku-sthuthi-aayirikkatte">Eesho Mishihaykku Sthuthi Aayirikkatte&lt;/h4>
&lt;img src="https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/img/sthuthi.jpg" width="180" width="100%" height="auto">
&lt;p>&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="ഈശ-മശഹയകക-സതത-ആയരകകടട">ഈശോ മിശിഹായ്ക്ക് സ്തുതി ആയിരിക്കട്ടെ&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>&lt;em>So, whether you eat or drink, or whatever you do, do everything for the glory of God.&lt;/em> (1 Cor 10:31)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Growing up, we were taught to say &lt;em>Eesho mishihaykku sthuthi aayirikkatte&lt;/em>, to our parents, our elders, fathers and sisters - not just as a sign of respect but also to give praise to the Lord. It is that virtue that we intend to teach and practice with the children this year. Throughout the year we will have several activities during class and outside class that will help the children build the virtue of giving praise, giving glory to God in all that they do. Our goal is to have every child in the mission comfortable to say &lt;em>Sthuthi&lt;/em> by the end of the academic year.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CCD Theme</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-theme-2024-2025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-theme-2024-2025/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="theme-of-the-year-2024---2025">&lt;strong>Theme of the Year 2024 - 2025&lt;/strong>&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Background:&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We introduced the “Theme of the Year” during the academic year 2023-24 to bring the student body, teachers and the parents together and focus on a common faith-based concept. Different grades/classes of the CCD program are at different stages of their faith formation journey. With the theme of the year, we have all classes work on the same concept. The theme is not an alternative to the CCD curriculum; the theme only acts as a complement to the curriculum and aims to enhance and strengthen the faith formation experience for students, teachers and parents.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 10:05:49 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission, is made up of vibrant, faithful people who serve our Mission and community in numerous ways – from worship, religious education and formation, sacramental preparation and spiritual development, to community outreach and social activities. We strive to be a welcoming community that reflects the heart, mercy and teachings of Christ, under the obedience of the Roman Catholic Church through the tradition of the Syro Malabar Rite. We pray you find, Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission to be a warm and welcoming place where you can deepen your faith by being a part of our Mission.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Announcements</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/announcements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/announcements/</guid><description>&lt;!--### Oct 15th, 2023
---

### Announcements from Sunday School

1. We have sent a detailed email about the camp to all registered families. We invite the community to attend Sunday Qurbana at camp with the children at 2:30pm celebrated by Fr.Joseph Alex and our mission Director Fr. James Joseph. We request your prayers for the success of this spiritual retreat for our children. 

2. A gentle reminder to families who are yet to pay $150 to cover CCD expenses. You can make this payment by cash or check made out to HFSMCM or donate through our online portal: 
https://holyfamilyseattle.org/donation/
3. Please save the date for *'Hallowed 2023'*, the All Saints day dress up competition for CCD students which will be conducted on *Sunday, November 5th* after Holy Qurbana here in the sanctuary. More details and the registration form will be posted soon in all our communication channels.
4. All parents are invited to a PTA meeting on Sunday, October 29th after Qurbana in the sanctuary. Please plan to attend this meeting and help support our children's faith formation activities.
 
### General Announcements

1. The Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission now has the option for &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://holyfamilyseattle.org/donation/">online donations&lt;/a>. We kindly ask that you prayerfully consider setting up recurring donations to support the church's activities. If you have any questions or concerns, please reach out to any of the trustees.
2. The Ward Based Ministry Assistance for Holy Mass for 29th October, will be coordinated by Saint Joseph’s Ward (Bothel, Woodinville, Everett, Mill Creek).
3. The Holy Mass for *next week, on Sunday, October 22nd, 2023, will be held at 2:30 PM at Don Bosco Camp* (https://maps.app.goo.gl/gtfUWd9UGgF2fpUQA).
4. Our Annual Calendar is already available in our Mission Website and in addition, we will be publishing a Physical paper based Annual Calendar for 2024, for which Advertisement space is available, please reach out to Trustees for more details. -->
&lt;h3 id="christmas-mass-december-24th-sunday-at-600-pm">&lt;b>Christmas Mass:&lt;/b> December 24th, Sunday at 6.00 PM&lt;/h3>
&lt;h3 id="venue-christ-the-king-ctk-lutheran-church-3730-148th-ave-se-bellevue-wa-98006">&lt;b>Venue:&lt;/b> Christ the King (CTK) Lutheran Church (3730 148th Ave SE, Bellevue, WA 98006)&lt;/h3>
&lt;/br>
&lt;/br>
&lt;/br>
&lt;h5 id="-weekly-announcements-in-detail-are-shared-in-church-whatsapp-and-facebook-groups">*** Weekly announcements in detail are shared in church whatsapp and facebook groups&lt;/h5>
&lt;hr></description></item><item><title>CCD Calendar</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/calendar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/calendar/</guid><description>&lt;div>
 &lt;h3>Monthly Events Calendar&lt;/h3>
 &lt;div class="container-iframe">
 &lt;iframe class="responsive-iframe" src="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?src=c_58ad3ab7313e894def101c6a623ad0ca167d12e96eee51c7c2eecec458672379%40group.calendar.google.com&amp;ctz=America%2FLos_Angeles" width="100%" height="auto" style="border: 0" frameborder="0">&lt;/iframe>
 &lt;/div>
 &lt;br> &lt;br>
 &lt;h3>Annual Calendar&lt;/h3>
 &lt;div class="container-iframe">
 &lt;iframe class="responsive-iframe" src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1VO-YwsI_vf5WddZP_nYJvIo9xnt6_CLf/preview" width="100%" height="auto" style="border: 0" frameborder="0" >&lt;/iframe>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>CCD Newsletter</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-newsletter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/ccd-newsletter/</guid><description>&lt;style>
.center {
 display: flex;
 justify-content: center;
 align-items: center;
}
&lt;/style>
&lt;div class = "center">
&lt;a href="https://heyzine.com/flip-book/e65050ae1e.html">CCD Newsletter - August 2024&lt;/a>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div class="container-iframe">
 &lt;iframe class="responsive-iframe" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" scrolling="no" src="https://heyzine.com/flip-book/e65050ae1e.html" style="border: 1px solid lightgray; width: 100%; ">&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/contact/</guid><description>&lt;div class="row">
 &lt;div class="col-6 col-12-mobilep">
 &lt;h3>Address&lt;/h3>
 &lt;p> 8512 122nd Ave NE, Suite 227, Kirkland, WA 98033&lt;/p>
 &lt;h3>Email&lt;/h3>
 &lt;p> smcseattle.trustees@gmail.com &lt;/p>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/div></description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/events/</guid><description>&lt;div>
 &lt;h3>Events Calendar&lt;/h3>
 &lt;div class="container-iframe">
 &lt;iframe class="responsive-iframe" src="https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?height=600&amp;wkst=1&amp;ctz=America%2FLos_Angeles&amp;showPrint=0&amp;src=c21jc2VhdHRsZS50cnVzdGVlc0BnbWFpbC5jb20&amp;src=NmVlNjY4ZTkzMzNmYTAxOTI2MGQ3MzlmODQ1YzY0ZWI0YjkwMTZkY2M4ZmE5ZjdiMGJhYWNhZTdiZDQ1ODYzMEBncm91cC5jYWxlbmRhci5nb29nbGUuY29t&amp;src=Y181OGFkM2FiNzMxM2U4OTRkZWYxMDFjNmE2MjNhZDBjYTE2N2QxMmU5NmVlZTUxYzdjMmVlY2VjNDU4NjcyMzc5QGdyb3VwLmNhbGVuZGFyLmdvb2dsZS5jb20&amp;color=%237CB342&amp;color=%23AD1457&amp;color=%23009688" style="border:solid 1px #777" width="800" height="600" frameborder="0" scrolling="no">&lt;/iframe>
 &lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;hr>
&lt;img src="https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/img/holy_week_2025.jpg" width="auto" height="auto">
&lt;hr></description></item><item><title>Online Donation</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/donation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/donation/</guid><description>&lt;p>All donations and payments to Holy Family Syro Malabar Catholic Mission can now be made through &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://get.tithe.ly/">Tithe.ly&lt;/a> which is built for churches and ministries to securely process your donations and payments.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://get.tithe.ly/">Tithe.ly&lt;/a> will issue a year-end giving statement for all your online donations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Your donations are greatly appreciated and especially needed to support and maintain our ministries. Please prayerfully consider to make a recurring donation. Thank you.&lt;/p>
&lt;style>
.center {
 display: flex;
 justify-content: center;
 align-items: center;
}
&lt;/style>
&lt;div class = "center">
&lt;button class="tithely-give-btn" style="background-color: #00DB72;font-family: inherit;font-weight: bold;font-size: 19px; padding: 15px 70px; border-radius: 4px; cursor: pointer; background-image: none; color: white; text-shadow: none; display: inline-block; float: none; border: none;" data-church-id="6374327">Donate&lt;/button>
&lt;/div>
&lt;script src="https://tithe.ly/widget/v3/give.js?3">&lt;/script>
&lt;script>
var tw = create_tithely_widget();
&lt;/script></description></item><item><title>Online Forms</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/online-forms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/online-forms/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfDiO44MWBj-LTiR71kJzGJU2BnfP-M2lF9xwPJF0uOj9CixQ/viewform">Holy Family Syro-Malabar Catholic Mission Registration&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSej3OrlHDINgv96XfJwlCVv3WmaYzUsMgly7zxFz6PiCtfkCg/viewform">Mass Intentions&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfHOlU2sGxsSL-PSFPCZu1_xvB0GwOWPW5IeQlyQsoi-9NY9g/viewform">Oppis&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Parish On Net</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/parish-on-net/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/parish-on-net/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://stthomas.parishon.net/seattle/site/login">ParishOnNet website&lt;/a> enables the head of a family to update the details of every one in the family. This data is confidential and would help Chicago diocese to plan better for Seattle SyroMalabar Community.&lt;/p>
&lt;div>
 &lt;h3>&lt;b>FAQs&lt;/b>&lt;/h3>
 &lt;p>&lt;b>1. What is ParishOnNet?&lt;/b>&lt;/p>
 &lt;p>ParishOnNet is an online church management system mandated by St. Thomas SyroMalabar Diocese of Chicago for its parishes and missions. It offers standard parish management features along with facilities for online payment and a parishioner portal.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Picnic Pre Order Form</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/picnic-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/picnic-order/</guid><description>&lt;div id="ff-compose">&lt;/div>
&lt;script async defer src="https://formfacade.com/include/103563710243545245113/form/1FAIpQLSeeFzqi8fA88st934ZQf_VY34vouJa5_V0RUTHJ9qKuvK86iA/classic.js?div=ff-compose">&lt;/script></description></item><item><title>Xmas Carol 2024</title><link>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/carol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://holyfamilyseattle.github.io/carol/</guid><description>&lt;table>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQQnbHvjvhOFQZhMVnpqIrnoAbXDkTEsCd938QvsJ0UHfiY">
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQRSqFo20IxDTpahuwYOea2lAUgk8npPxZ4bX57KVHtppV4">&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQQkg7lJj4VESKoEuVI8aX3eAbdoyMKNzC9f_gAk9z-I9_c">&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQQOw2ESLIS1TbP1LQ4XGY4XAaZ2y3Q-PnDRIUKqAa7CbCk">&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQQwWj22JsCySrE0tCcr-7hjAQvtAViCiDUBYmsPsuRE0Go">&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQR0f0Nuh2sdSYV0-HvBtI93ARKRqy_s613AUq0kigRvjhs">&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQQqvT8N9VhWTZksYguN7h0KAf_qonCmCx89ntrZnFBLlFY">&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQSspxPBKGoGR5odQ9Ncr6rVAfDkRHeyhYTka5qi7ROyc7U">&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQSDg5SqCmBDT7j16aUaNjspAXItw75KlaJRCARsvhHfi50">&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
 &lt;tr>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQRg-UUez-rxSpXx18SckEWQAaFSc0VZc5YGf3S8qqTV0Hw">&lt;/td>
 &lt;td>&lt;img src="https://1drv.ms/i/c/4a509ecdfd9185d9/IQQ5v8ce9CJMRIKToGpFqsx6AUp7dkOPc6ybgyFvL1QUWc8">&lt;/td>
 &lt;/tr>
&lt;/table>
&lt;hr></description></item></channel></rss>